<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"	xmlns:excerpt="http://wordpress.org/export/1.0/excerpt/"	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"	xmlns:wp="http://wordpress.org/export/1.0/"><channel>	<title>eurotrip '09</title>	<link></link>	<description>a jaunt through west europe</description>	<pubDate>Thu Jun 18 13:17:37 -0700 2009</pubDate>	<generator>http://posterous.com</generator>	<language>en</language>	<wp:wxr_version>1.0</wp:wxr_version>	<wp:base_site_url>http://iamthedivebomber.posterous.com</wp:base_site_url>	<wp:base_blog_url>http://iamthedivebomber.posterous.com</wp:base_blog_url>		<image>		<url>http://files.posterous.com/user_profile_pics/615262/headshot.jpg</url>		<title>eurotrip '09</title>		<link>http://iamthedivebomber.posterous.com</link>	</image>	<item>	<title>Days 4-6</title>	<link>http://iamthedivebomber.posterous.com/posterous-re-days-2-3</link>	<pubDate>Mon Jul 06 16:14:00 -0700 2009</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sergey Karayev]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://iamthedivebomber.posterous.com/posterous-re-days-2-3</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Day 4</strong><p />It&acute;s actually day 11 as I write this, so I&acute;m starting to forget some things. There&acute;s little time to sit down and write stuff, especially because computer time is scarce in hostels. And when I find some time and an open computer, I rarely want to write anything, just read the New York Times. Although I&acute;m having ambivalent feelings about the value of memories, I still think it&acute;s good to write all this down.<p /> Lisbon was entered via a morning EasyJet flight from London. On the plane, I slept for the two hours flight duration, and it was the only sleep I got that night. Stepping off the plane, the first thing I noticed was the heat. The airport was a buffer zone for language, mixing Portuguese with English and Spanish. Outside, at the bus stop, it was all Portuguese. Strangely, I did not feel nervous. I followed pretty good directions to get to my hostel: the Aerobus 42 went to the Grand Arch (it&acute;s truly grand), I walked under it and turned left onto Rua Augusta, then turned right on the fourth street. On the way, an old man approached me, holding something in the palm of his hand. His skin was leathery from decades of sun, and he was wearing an old dusty suit. He spoke multiple languages (&uml;French? Very good French!&uml;) but I just kept saying no and walking. In his hand were four brown blocks, each about the size of a packet of gum. I certainly did not understand what they were.<p /> Easy Hostel was super nice! Good interior, really open lounge with a lot of couches and those beanbag chair deals in front of the TV, three nice computers, FREE LAUNDRY, free lockers, good beds, and a nice kitchen with solid breakfast. For 14 euros! By the way, the entirety of Europe in my experience has no ventilation in the bathrooms. After I checked in and put my bag in the luggage room, I introduced myself to the three people in the lounge. Larissa, Timur, and Logan were the names, and they were all from California UC&acute;s. They were going out to lunch and asked if I wanted to join them. It was precisely what I sought to hear, and so off we were.</p><p /><div>Larissa got a recommendation from someone at reception, and so we looked for a place to eat on only one street. We found a place with the most locals and went there. Nobody knew any Portuguese, so my little cheat sheet ripped out of a Rick Steves phrasebook got some preparatory use. But fortunately, our waiter, Nelson, spoke English. Nelson was sweet, he complimented Larissa&acute;s choice of cod and recommended that we get the traditional Portuguese wine (&uml;White wine, red wine, green wine. Let me recommend the green.&uml;). &uml;House wine&uml; comes in a vase and is cheap cheap. Green wine tastes like less bubbly, sweeter Prosecco, and is absolutely commendable. I got steak with mushrooms, also delicious, for a total cost of about 10 euro.<p /> After lunch, we took a tram (like in San Francisco, rickety streetcars go up and down hills. Unlike in San Francisco, some streets are so narrow that you can touch the buildings if you reach out a hand) somewhere, got off at the last stop, and then started walking toward the Castillo, a big castle that presides on a hill over Lisbon. The neighborhood is called Alfama, and it is incredibly steep. On the way, we heard a bunch of older folk singing in the street accompanied by an accordion, saw a lot of grafitti, a cat sleeping on the hood of a car, and some nice views of Lisbon's red roofs. These are all pictures, but I can't post them just yet.<p /> Castillo featured amazing views of Lisbon, medieval style castle walls, and peacocks. I really enjoy views from high places, so I sat and took it in while everyone else found the bathroom. Coming back to the hostel, we were tired. I can't quite remember what I did until the evening, when I went out with the same folk again. We walked the streets of the Bairro Alto looking for a bar with music, and found a pretty cool one. It featured Cuban music that night, and had people spilling all over the narrow street outside. By the way, old Lisbon is three neighborhoods: flat Baixa, where the hostel was, is flanked by hilly Bairro Alto and Alfama. All streets are lined with old buildings of various colors, a lot of them covered in different tile patterns. By the way, the image below composes most of the reason for why I went to Lisbon--the cover of some electronic music album called Lisbon, I have not heard it.</div><p /><div><div class='p_embed p_image_embed'><a href="http://getfile9.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/iamthedivebomber/Gqq6YmDUgAXCJv0AUBBoG65CmvJ58Oen4eIrW0uWVqrPheQmEkw0Wpq0i7AM/cover2260.jpg"><img alt="Cover2260" src="http://getfile9.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/iamthedivebomber/Gqq6YmDUgAXCJv0AUBBoG65CmvJ58Oen4eIrW0uWVqrPheQmEkw0Wpq0i7AM/cover2260.jpg" /></a></div> <br />We stood outside for a while, enjoying some sangria and backing up onto the sidewalk as the occassional taxi insisted on going through the crowded street. Some local guy danced with Timur a little bit. Timur and Logan are roommates at some UC, and Larissa met Timur in Italy where they are both studying. At the end of the night, I successfully purchased some sort of pork sandiwch from a woman who was cooking them up outside of her house, in the street. With a bit of ketchup and hot sauce, it was a tasty end.<p /> <strong><br />Day 5</strong><p />This morning I was hanging out in the lounge, talking to some girls who just got in, and a guy named Sergio, who's moving to Seattle to be a Product Manager at Microsoft. He's from Harvard (is it condescending when people from Harvard say they go to a college in Boston?) and discovered that he likes computer science even though his major was something else. A girl named Cherissa, heretofore sitting quietly in the corner, asked everyone in the room if anyone feels like going to lunch, because she's starving. Sergio and I did, and so I took them back to the same street as yesterday. Indeed, we went to the same place, which was the best decision, because Nelson recognized me and was even friendlier. He talked to us, recommended the grilled fish platter (amazing) and brought us little half glasses of port at the end of the meal, gratis. Cherissa is a student at University of Ohio, I think, is from Houston, and wants to go to veterinary school. Nelson kept refusing to bring us the check, so we spent a good 2 or 3 hours at the place, and so talked pretty extensively. When we got back to the hostel, Cherissa and I decided to go check out Lisbon, the parts I haven't seen. We walked for hours through Bairro Alto, the Jardim Botanico (garden), some park with a sweet climable structure made of rope, and a Basilico, where we observed Mass. I was mega hungry when we got back to the hostel, but I could not find anyone who wanted to get dinner. I think I walked around for a long time looking for something, but ended up getting silly bruschetta toast from some touristy place.<p /> <br /><strong>Day 6</strong><p />First lazy day. I hung around the lounge in the morning, watched Super Bad with Sergio, then, having failed to convince him to get lunch (the guy's an ascetic), ventured out on my own and got a plate called something like "meats of Portugal" at some cafe full of locals. It was a bunch of second-tier cuts on potatoes and rice: ends of sausages, really fatty pork, and beef brisket. With the unsurprising exception of pork, it was delicious. I loved the black sausage in particular, also known as blood sausage. Then I came back to the hostel and I can't remember what I did until dinner time, when I, again, ventured out alone. Tired of looking for places that don't look too touristy and aren't expensive, I just went back to Nelson's cafe. (Nelson: "Ah! You lost all the women!") I got some fish and a glass of port. After dinner, I drank tea and ate a pastry I picked up on the way back, and then hustled to the train station for an overnighter to Madrid. Now I remember what I did during the day: I went to the train station and spent the longest time behind some Australians as they failed to comprehend what the ticket vendor was trying to explain to them. A Eurail pass for Portugal and Spain is no good: you have to make reservations for everything, which means going to the train station in person instead of just buying tickets, which are pretty cheap in the first place, on the internet, I'll probably end up losing money and time because of my pass. I live and learn.<p /> </div>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Day 4It s actually day 11 as I write this, so I m starting to forget some things. There s little time to sit down and write stuff, especially because computer time is scarce in hostels. And when I find some time and an open computer, I rarely w...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Mon Jul 06 16:14:00 -0700 2009</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>Mon Jul 06 16:14:00 -0700 2009</wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_id>1325771</wp:post_id>	<wp:post_name>posterous-re-days-2-3</wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>Europe First Day</title>	<link>http://iamthedivebomber.posterous.com/europe-first-day</link>	<pubDate>Thu Jun 25 11:44:32 -0700 2009</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sergey Karayev]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://iamthedivebomber.posterous.com/europe-first-day</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[Dang, I&#39;m pretty tired! Today I spent 15 hours in transit, and now around 12 hours in london.<p />Transitwas fine: there were clear skies everywhere Seattle to Atlanta, and Iwas overcome by the splendor of the Rocky Mountains. I wish I couldpost pictures. On the flight from ATL to London I talked to myneighbor, a black woman in her 30s from England who teaches at aprivate school in Atlanta. She was a good conversationalist. I alsowatched two movies: Gran Torino and Uninvited. Unfortunately, I didn&#39;tget to finish Uninvited, because we landed. Also unfortunately, I didget to finish Gran Torino, and so I saw Clint Eastwood lie in aChrist-like pose after rasping his way through the movie he alsodirected and produced.<p />Most of the London time was spent walking. Initial observations:drivers are crazy and routinely drive on the left side of the road, itis illegal not to jaywalk, every girl has skinny jeans, and the Tube(subway) has got to be ventilated somewhere in hell. Anyway, I musthave walked about 20 miles, and for about 10 miles I was looking for aplace to eat fabled <i>curry</i>, supposedly the new British national dish. I swear, there was <b>one street </b> with open Indian places. The one I went to wasn&#39;t any good. I no longer want to try this <i>curry</i>. Tomorrow I&#39;ll try to eat fish and chips, but today I just wasn&#39;t hungry enough.<p />Also, a pigeon flew by close enough to hit my face with its wings. I also didn&#39;t figure out that they <b>walk </b>onthe left side, too, so I kept bumping into people for most of the day.I don&#39;t have a watch and keep thinking that it&#39;s later than what itactually is. It&#39;s 7:30pm here, but I&#39;m too tired not to go to sleep--Ifell asleep on the tube and in a park already.#<p />Overall, today London seemed far more commercial than historic. Itwas like a giant beautiful shopping mall, with a place for the Queen tolive. Tomorrow I&#39;ll try to focus more on the historic landmarks, andalso go to British Museum, because I want to see mummies. Karl&#39;s comingtomorrow.<p />I probably won&#39;t post every day, but maybe every few days.]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Dang, I'm pretty tired! Today I spent 15 hours in transit, and now around 12 hours in london.Transit was fine: there were clear skies everywhere Seattle to Atlanta, and I was overcome by the splendor of the Rocky Mountains. I wish I could post pic...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Thu Jun 25 11:44:32 -0700 2009</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>Thu Jun 25 11:44:32 -0700 2009</wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_id>1151146</wp:post_id>	<wp:post_name>europe-first-day</wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>Paris</title>	<link>http://iamthedivebomber.posterous.com/paris-1846</link>	<pubDate>Sat Jun 05 02:47:08 -0700 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sergey Karayev]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://iamthedivebomber.posterous.com/paris-1846</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div style="font-family: arial, sans-serif; border-collapse: collapse; font-size: 13px;">It may be important to state that one clear evening in July of last year, I waited in vain for the last metro train from the Eiffel tower, on the yellow line. There were a few people waiting at the station, but one by one they were leaving. Finally a janitor made it clear to the holdouts that indeed there was no train coming. Emerging aboveground, I decided to walk back to my hostel, on the other side of the city. I figured it wouldn't take more than two hours; a taxi seemed wasteful and buses imponderable.<p /><div>Below is a map with my route overlaid. It must have been around 1 a.m. and I didn't see many people.</div><p /><div>&nbsp;<div class='p_embed p_image_embed'><a href="http://getfile4.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/iamthedivebomber/TyXEQuONRiS8AjdYi8t1uEViCCuuTqrQX2nyjoZcQ9bhm37TJzPDeJTmgABH/my_paris_walk.png"><img alt="My_paris_walk" src="http://getfile4.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/iamthedivebomber/TyXEQuONRiS8AjdYi8t1uEViCCuuTqrQX2nyjoZcQ9bhm37TJzPDeJTmgABH/my_paris_walk.png" /></a></div></div><p /><div>Maintaining a journal while traveling is difficult and, I've decided, unnecessary. The most important thing I hope to have taken away from my sojourn is a new perspective on time. Rooted in a place and routine, with each day resembling the days previous, my sense of time becomes warped. Days stretch to form a canvas on which to paint the fruits of a long list of things to do. There are few hard deadlines, and if I don't do something today, tomorrow it will probably get done, or the day after, and definitely by next week. Days blend together, such that I expand the possibilities of one day to all future days.</div><p /><div>On the road, moving from place to place with nothing long-term to work on, geography defines the things that are possible. It becomes clear that if I don't do something that can only be done in this place, it will never be done, for tomorrow I will be somewhere else. Days are a block of post-it notes instead of a long ticker tape: I better be satisfied with whatever I sketch on one, for it will be torn off tomorrow.</div><p /><div>This travel-mode view of time seems closer to the real state of affairs. Each day really is different from previous ones, if only because the latter are gone forever. It is okay and at times necessary to not do anything worthwhile in a given day; or to work on one thing intensely for a few days, but I should do so with intention, and not because I've ceased to notice time's course. I am thankful for having the chance to travel and to visit relatives last summer. This summer I will be biking from the Canadian border to the Mexican border along the West coast--a journey equally awesome!</div></div>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[It may be important to state that one clear evening in July of last year, I waited in vain for the last metro train from the Eiffel tower, on the yellow line. There were a few people waiting at the station, but one by one they were leaving. Finall...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Sat Jun 05 02:47:08 -0700 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>Sat Jun 05 02:47:08 -0700 2010</wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_id>19746139</wp:post_id>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>Days 2-3</title>	<link>http://iamthedivebomber.posterous.com/days-2-3</link>	<pubDate>Wed Jul 01 10:04:20 -0700 2009</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sergey Karayev]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://iamthedivebomber.posterous.com/days-2-3</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[Day 2<p />London is a fashionable city, and especially having confined my walking to the West End, I felt extra unstylish. I only met one person in my 4-bed dorm at the Quest Hostel, where I slept last night--an Italian guy named Flavio who was in London for a week, mostly to shop. In the evening, I was talking to him a little bit, and told him I liked the pants that were in a bag by his bed. He got excited and said that they&#39;re on sale at some place called Topman, right outside the Oxford Circus station (where most nice big stores seem to be), and cost only 1.5 pounds. Although I asked him again if he really meant that they cost less than 2 pounds, I think we had a miscommunication, because this morning I went to that store and they were 15 pounds. I still bought them, and also a sweatshirt. That took a while, and I felt silly.<p />I wasn´t due to meet Karl at our new hostel (Palmer&#39;s Lodge) until 2pm, so I went to the British Museum for a little bit. Unfortunately, I only had time to see the Egyptian stuff, which was 100% impressive. Seeing really ridiculous stuff like giant heads and winged lions and giant pyramids and mummification made me think about how our culture is also ridiculous with its news shows and CGI movies and cubicles in really tall buildings and plastic surgery.<p />I met Karl, we checked in to our room (a 6-bed dorm), rested a bit, then went to the West End where I walked around yesterday, this time looking for fish and chips. Once again, there weren´t any dedicated fish and chips places, it´s just pub fare. We ended up at a place called White Horse, where I got fish n&#39; chips and a London Pride beer, which was creamily delicious. I think after we walked around a bit more, and then got on a tour bus that took us all around town and showed us how far its glories spread. Karl was nodding off to sleep for some of it. There were fascist obnoxious drunk germans at the back of the bus, and a nice New Jersey family at the front. The husband told us to become federal investigators, because of the pension. I think we just went home and slept after that. Oh, we also went to the hostel bar, but nothing was happening. We also took a surprisingly long time trying to sink two pool balls in. What the English call pool is not what we call pool; that´s billiards. I think at some point in the day we also drank like 15 pounds worth of lemonade because we kept refilling the 1.50 cup before paying for it, and threw a frisbee around.<p />Day 3<p />We got too late of a start and missed breakfast, and the Tube line our hostel is on was undergoing maintenance, so we waited for a while for a bus and then in traffic. We got off at Baker Street (where Sherlock lived or worked--I can´t remember), and spotted a sweet cafe that served Full English Breakfast for like five quid (that´s pounds). A Full English breakfast, advertised in a lot of cafes, consists of an egg, bacon, sausage, beans, toast, and tea. Ours was delicious, and made us feel so full that we just wanted to sit down. Since Karl had to go to some out-of-the way train station (Liverpool) to buy his ferry ticket to Rotterdam, or so he thought, we decided to get on the Tube and go there. Unfortunately, we ran into massive closures and delays, and stations that felt like the intro to Half-Life 2. Finally, we made it there, Karl was given a phone number to call, and I just hung out for a while, and ran into my first pay toilet in Europe. Eventually, we made our way to the West End, and walked down to Westminster Bridge to do a guided walk that was described in a book by Rick Steves, a chapter of which was in my possession.<p />The Houses of Parliament is probably the most impressive building I have seen. It&#39;s incredibly ornate--Karl and I pretended to have trouble believing that reality is a powerful enough graphics engine to render it. So to speak! Then, as a detour from the guided walk, which would have taken us by Downing Street and some military buildings and up to Trafalgar Square, we walked over to Westminster Abbey. A terrible affliction beset me here: thousands of tiny fruit flies kept landing on my yellow shirt, seriously freaking Karl out. He eventually freaked me out, and so I had to take off my shirt in the middle of everything and shake it out and stuff. But when I put it back on, they kept landing on it! Thinking that they were coming from my bag, I took my shirt off and went through my bag one by one item, but it was all clean. The shirt meanwhile, was covered by more flies. We figured out that they were attracted to the color, and noticed it on other people and also (unpleasantly) on the hood of my sweatshirt, which I was wearing in lieu of the t&#39;shirt which I left somewhere in Westminster.<p />In the confusion I had forgot the guidebook by the Abbey. So instead of finishing the tour, we just walked back to Oxford Circus to buy t-shirts. Properly clothed again, I was ready to do the next thing on our list: see a play or a musical. There was a sweet Waiting for Godot playing at some theater, with Patrick Stewart and Sir Ian McKellen, but they didn´t have any non-obstructed seats available. We ended up seeing Avenue Q, which was a silly decision I guess because of how American it is. Then again, all the other musicals they have are also American. Before the play, we ate another basket of fish and chips, and this time I got Guinness and then a Spitfire. After the play, we walked through Soho trying to find a bar or a club or something to go to, but they were all full of people who were a little too old for us, except for one, where they were too young. We just got belgian waffles and a coffee. While we were sitting in front of the awesome theater that was showing We Will Rock You, a Queen musical, this young guy started talking to us. He asked what I was listening to? I said Animal Collective. He said, What the hell is that? I didn´t know what he wanted from us, so I said Electronic. That set him off on a long argument that music needs not only the brain but also the heart. Periodically he threw in that Michael Jackson was a paragon of music, so maybe he was drunk and grieving. He was really nice, though, but we didn´t do anything but agree with him.<p />Eventually, we made it back to the hostel, where Karl was just going to spend the night in the lounge and I was going to hang out a bit and then get a bus to the Luton airport in time for my 5:30 check-in to Lisbon. We met three girls from Florida who just arrived, but they were going to bed. From them I learned about some district called Camden that´s like Capitol Hill in Seattle, except infintely better, I imagine. We wanted to go out there, but by the time we got ready, it was too late for me to make it back and catch my bus comfortably. While I was waiting for Karl, I introduced myself to some girl in the lounge, and for the rest of the night we hung out in the front yard with her and her friend, both from Germany, and a local fox who ate the potato chips we fed it. I don´t get why, but they offered us a place to stay if we were ever in their town. I guess we should have said something simillar, but I don´t think we yet understood how quickly people become friends while travelling. I don´t think I understand it still. At last, it was time for me to go catch the 3:20am bus to the airport.]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Day 2London is a fashionable city, and especially having confined my walking to the West End, I felt extra unstylish. I only met one person in my 4-bed dorm at the Quest Hostel, where I slept last night--an Italian guy named Flavio who was in Lond...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Wed Jul 01 10:04:20 -0700 2009</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>Wed Jul 01 10:04:20 -0700 2009</wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_id>1249689</wp:post_id>	<wp:post_name>days-2-3</wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item></channel></rss>