<item>
	<title>Preface</title>
	<link>http://bestcoast.posterous.com/preface-18</link>
	<pubDate>Mon Jun 28 07:27:00 -0700 2010</pubDate>
	
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sergey Karayev]]></dc:creator>
	
	

	<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://bestcoast.posterous.com/preface-18</guid>
	<description></description>
	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Thanks to my family, co-workers, and friends, I am fortunate enough to be able to go on a five-week long bicycling adventure, starting today. My friend <a href="http://samzipper.com">Sam Zipper</a> and I are setting out to cross these United States from north to south, border to border, along what is surely one of the most scenic coastlines in the world. We will start by crossing the Canadian border from Sidney, BC to Anacortes, WA, and plan to end by triumphantly entering Tijuana. The overall trip length should be around 1700 miles.</p>
<p><br />That does sound daunting, but the first couple of days are really easy. Today we drive to Port Angeles, ferry to Victoria, bike 20 miles to Sidney, take another ferry to Anacortes, and hang out! I plan on at least one nap. The next day, all we need to do is 40 miles to Port Townsend along Whidbey Island--a first-rate location. <p /> <iframe scrolling="no" marginheight="0" marginwidth="0" src="http://maps.google.com/maps/ms?ie=UTF8&amp;hl=en&amp;msa=0&amp;msid=105022987179455679401.00048a1503a63430df390&amp;ll=48.385709,-123.021706&amp;spn=0.535126,0.818069&amp;output=embed" frameborder="0" height="350" width="425"></iframe><br /><small>View <a href="http://maps.google.com/maps/ms?ie=UTF8&amp;hl=en&amp;msa=0&amp;msid=105022987179455679401.00048a1503a63430df390&amp;ll=48.385709,-123.021706&amp;spn=0.535126,0.818069&amp;source=embed" style="color: #0000ff; text-align: left;">First week summer 2010</a> in a larger map</small> <p /> I hope to post regular updates from the road here. As we lack a computer but do have a phone with a data plan, most times they may be just a photo and a silly caption. I don't really know what to expect from a tour yet, but that's half the fun!</p>]]></content:encoded>
	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Thanks to my family, co-workers, and friends, I am fortunate enough to be able to go on a five-week long bicycling adventure, starting today. My friend Sam Zipper and I are setting out to cross these United States from north to south, border to bo...]]></excerpt:encoded>	

	<wp:post_date>Mon Jun 28 07:27:00 -0700 2010</wp:post_date>
	<wp:post_date_gmt>Mon Jun 28 07:27:00 -0700 2010</wp:post_date_gmt>
	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
	<wp:post_id>21396372</wp:post_id>
	<wp:post_name>preface</wp:post_name>
	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>

	
</item>
